poemsource.com 2019-04-12

# Poemsource.com Privacy Policy

At PoemSource.com we are dedicated to protecting your data and privacy.

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use PoemSource.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. This will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

PoemSource.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.

## About Our Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that PoemSource.com stores on your computer, which your browser provides to PoemSource.com each time you return to the site. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their use of our website, and their website access preferences.  

## Google Analytics Cookies

PoemSource.com uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics collects demographic and interest data, and generates statistical and other information about website use, by means of cookies. These cookies are kept on your computer. 

We share this information with Google, which will store and use this information on its servers. Google's privacy policy is available at: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>.

PoemSource.com uses information from Google Analytics to track the number of visits to the website, browsers and operating systems. No personally identifiable information is obtained from these cookies. We use the information that Google Analytics generates relating to our website to create reports about the use of the site. These reports allow us to update the site and improve your usage of it.

If you do not wish your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you can install its opt-out browser extension or add-on... [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)  

## Advertising Cookies

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our website. These are:

Google Adsense who also deliver these providers; <https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/9012903>

and   
[MediaNet  
](http://www.medianet.com.au/privacy-policy/)[Sovrn](https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/). There may be some providers that Sovrn uses that are not included in the Google List above.  For a full list, please [review this page](https://www.sovrn.com/dbm-vendor-whitelist/).   

These companies use cookies and web beacons in their ads to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. We share this information with these companies, but do not provide them with any personally identifiable information for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information from our website.

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.  

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative's multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.  

For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at  **infoah@poemsource.com  **and contact AdThrive at [info@adthrive.com](mailto:info@adthrive.com). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)

 _You may opt out of personalized ads for over 125 different ad networks._ [For 'How To' info, click here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/).

## Opting Out Of Google Ads

Some third-party advertisements are served by Google. Google's cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visits to other sites on the Web. You may opt out of personalized ads by visiting the [Google ad opt-out page.](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated)  (NB: Google has country-specific versions of this URL, so use the one for your country or region.)  

## Affiliate Products And Services

We receive an affiliate commission for some of the products sold on PoemSource.com

We use Amazon as an affiliate services platform.

By clicking on a product or service link, you consent to that platform's use of cookies, as outlined in the link below.

Read the [Amazon Privacy Policy](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=508088).

## Refusing Cookies

You can set your browser to accept or refuse all cookies automatically, or notify you when a cookie is being requested. Taking this action should not cause a problem with the continued use of our site. Consult the Help section of your browser for guidance on how to refuse all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is requested.

If you choose to refuse PoemSource.com’s cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.

## Personally Identifiable information

PoemSource.com may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes:

• To run and operate our site.

• To display content on the site correctly.

• To improve customer service.

• To help us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

• To personalize your user experience.

• To understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site.

• To improve our site.

• To improve our products and services.

• To run a promotion, contest, survey or other site feature.

• To send information to you that you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.

• To send periodic emails, which may include electronic newsletters and/or autoresponder series of emails.

• To respond to your enquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

PoemSource.com may collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our site, register on the site, or fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site.

## Submitting Content

If you submit content to us, we will ask for your name and email address. Photos you include with your submission, or details in your submission, may personally identify you.

If you request to be notified about comments on any content you submit to us, or request to be notified when others submit content, we will require your first name and your email address.

## Social Connections

This site lets you share content with your friends and followers on various social media platforms. 

Below are links to the privacy policies of:

### You Have The Choice To Refuse 

You can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information and visit our site anonymously. However, it may prevent you from engaging in certain site-related activities.

If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. We will use personal information received from you for internal purposes only and will not sell it or provide it to third parties.

We also collect each visitor's IP address, which helps us combat spam and fraud. We do not use IP addresses for any other purpose.

PoemSource.com contains links to other websites that may be of interest to you. However, once you have used them to leave our site, we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you provide while visiting such sites. These sites are not governed by this privacy statement. Always exercise caution by reviewing the privacy statement of the website in question before continuing to use it.

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information  

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you whenever you interact with our site.

Non-personally identifiable information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your method of connecting to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider you used, and other similar information.  

## Children's Privacy Protection  

This website is directed to adults. It is not directed to children under the age of 16. We operate our site in compliance with current regulations. Anyone under the age of 16 must provide parental consent to use this site. We do not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 16 years of age.  

## Release of Information  

If we sell PoemSource.com the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale so that the service provided to you may continue.

In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make.  

## Data Storage

Personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information collected by this site is stored on our host's servers.

That host is SiteSell Inc., located at 1000 Saint-Jean Boulevard, Suite 702, Pointe-Claire, QC H9R 5P1 Canada.  

## How You Can Correct or Remove Information  

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personally identifiable information.

If you have submitted personally identifiable information through our website and would like to download and review that information, [click on this link](https://www.poemsource.com/gdpr-review.html). 

You can also request to edit or delete any of your information from the servers by [clicking on this link](https://www.poemsource.com/gdpr-request.html).

## Updates and Effective Date  

PoemSource.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy.

If there is a material change in our cookie and privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that those practices have changed and provide a link to the updated privacy policy.

We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.  

## Agreeing to Terms  

If you do not agree to PoemSource.com's Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not consent to the setting of cookies and the collection and storage of your personally identifiable information.

Your explicit consent indicates acceptance of this privacy policy in its entirety.

Last updated: November 22, 2018.

[ Home](https://www.poemsource.com/) > Privacy Policy
